{
    "id": "f6a7a5056be747d08867d7d100812bf6",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They worked hard ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to win",
                "to winning",
                "winning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "335facb6fc7741238cb63ce5a1728172"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ................................... to do the right thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough sensible",
                "sensible enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7b42820e6914adc874a222c1babb4da"
        },
        {
            "question": "The problem was .................................. difficult for the students to solve.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7e054337a1b4f4fb8992dde99aa42c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ........................................ late for us to start a new lesson.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0cfa82e823d645438e8d9e1401c1b7cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager appointed James ..................................... the accounts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing",
                "to do",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1944ff85d19a461d9daf901717dc7c85"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went to the theater ........................................... a movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "seeing",
                "to seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d426bc88403423cb0b673a810c8be41"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................., I have no interest in politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Be frank",
                "To be frank",
                "Being frank"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d354b3aa133d48fcaed5acd7c71c142b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man took out a knife ....................................... all of us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to fright",
                "to frighten",
                "frightening"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae02fda416b8455ea92e6462d967edb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is Maryâ€™s duty ........................................ old stamps.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collecting",
                "to collect",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2052fb4240364b09ad83d5283e8bac5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The men held a meeting ..................................... a manager for the company.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to elect",
                "electing",
                "to electing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "553a1fa0eaf54cc58ac8cf95dc4fed0b"
        }
    ]
}